[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Lunar seas are actually plains of gabbro and this rock. The same rock is also a main component of the surface of Mars.", "correct_answer": "Basalt", "incorrect_answers": ["Obsidian", "Andesite", "Granulite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Whoopi Goldberg portray in the 1999 TV movie Alice in Wonderland?", "correct_answer": "Cheshire Cat", "incorrect_answers": ["The Duchess", "The Queen of Hearts", "The Mock Turtle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest wolf species on the planet as well as the largest wild representative of the Canidae family?", "correct_answer": "Grey wolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Polar wolf", "Black wolf", "Red wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Fight for the Future Begins was the tag line for which movie?", "correct_answer": "The Matrix", "incorrect_answers": ["Saving Private Ryan", "Lord Of The Rings : Return Of The King", "Terminator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Yorkshire Terriers are the smallest breed of dog in the world.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the enlisted national garments are African, while the fourth one is Norwegian. Which one?", "correct_answer": "Bunad", "incorrect_answers": ["Sanafil", "Dashiki", "Boubou"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the cockroaches ability to survive in hard times?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They are able to slow down their heart rate.", "Cockroaches can survive radiation up to 15 times stronger than the lethal dose for humans.", "Some roaches can survive without food for about one month."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you broil, where is the direct heat source?", "correct_answer": "Above the food", "incorrect_answers": ["Below the food", "There is no direct heat source; it uses indirect heat", "Surrounds the food"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ink changes its color on different paper.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The music for the movie The Conversation was composed before the movie was shot. Name the composer who was the directors brother-in-law.", "correct_answer": "David Shire", "incorrect_answers": ["Randy Newman", "John Williams", "Paul Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2004 movie starring Ryan Gosling and Rachel McAdams, was about the summer love of a young teenage couple that are eventually separated due to social differences.", "correct_answer": "The Notebook", "incorrect_answers": ["Love Actually", "Saving Private Ryan", "Titanic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What culinary miracle does Bruce Nolan perform in the cafeteria in the comedy \u2018Bruce Almighty\u2019?", "correct_answer": "He splits his tomato soup in half.", "incorrect_answers": ["He fries an egg with a single look.", "He turns the snowfall into marshmallows.", "He transforms a chair into a chocolate cake."]}]